So I hope you enjoyed that whirlwind tour of Google Colab.
구글 콜랍의 급속한 탐방을 즐기셨길 바라요
Here's just a little screenshot example of how easy it is to use it.
얼마나 사용이 쉬운지 스크린샷으로 보여드릴게요
You can just put in a bunch of code.
그냥 코드 뭉치를 Put만 하면 돼요
This is of course, hugging face code that we're going to be getting deep into very, very soon.
이건 물론 포옹하는 얼굴 코드죠 아주 곧 깊이 다룰 거예요
And in this case, I used the flux model, which is you may have noticed it was one of the top trending
이 경우 플럭스 모델을 사용했어요 가장 트렌드되는 모델 중 하나란 걸 눈치채셨을 겁니다 얼굴을
models when we were looking at models in hugging face.
껴안는 모델들을 보면요
It is a text to image generation model from Black Forest that is a particularly, uh, exciting in that
블랙 포레스트에서 나온 텍스트 이미지 생성 모델로 아주 강력한 오픈 소스 이미지 생성
it's one of the really strong open source image generation models.
모델 중 하나라는 점에서 특히 흥미롭죠
And I prompted it with a futuristic class full of students learning AI coding in the surreal style of
초현대적인 달리의 인공지능 코딩을 배우는 학생들로 가득한 미래적인 수업으로 프롬프트했죠
Uh, and this is what came up, which is wonderful, wonderful.
그래서 나온 게 이거예요 정말 훌륭하죠
Uh, and so it gives you a sense of how quickly you can use Google Colab to be, uh, working with,
구글 Colab을 얼마나 빨리 사용할 수 있는지 알 수 있죠 클라우드에서 고성능
uh, high powered GPUs in the cloud.
GPU와 작업하기 위해서요
And with that, we, uh, take a moment to take stock of our progress.
이와 함께 진행 상황을 잠시 점검해 보죠
We are now ready.
이제 준비됐어요
You are well positioned to be beginning on your open source adventure.
오픈 소스 모험을 시작하기에 좋은 위치예요
Uh, in addition to what you could already do confidently coding with frontier APIs and building multimodal
개척형 API로 자신 있게 코딩하고 다중 모듈 인공지능 어시스턴트 제작을 하는
AI assistants, you can now navigate through Hugging Face and Google Colab and you are ready for action.
것 외에도 이제는 포옹하는 얼굴과 구글 Colab을 탐색할 수 있습니다 이제 준비가 다 됐죠
So next time you're going to be able to run open source models, there's two different levels of API
다음에 오픈 소스 모델을 실행할 땐 얼굴을 안는 동작엔 두 가지 API 레벨이 있어요 그게
in hugging face, and you're going to understand what that means and what they are.
무슨 뜻인지 그게 뭔지 이해하게 될 거예요
And then we're going to start with the first of those, which is called pipelines.
이제 첫 번째 것부터 시작할게요 파이프라인이라고 하죠
You're going to be able to use pipelines for a bunch of different AI tasks, including generating text,
다양한 인공지능 작업에 대해 파이프라인을 사용할 수 있습니다 오픈 소스 모델을
images and audio using open source models.
이용해 텍스트, 이미지, 오디오 생성을 포함해서요
I can't wait.
기대되네요